# Final Project Sanbercode Batch 40 - Kelompok 4

1. Indra Budiman
  * Test Case: module PIM and Performance
  * Manual Testing: module PIM and Performance
  * Automation Testing:
    - module PIM feature sucess add new employee
    - module PIM feature failed add new employee
    - module PIM feature sucess search an employee
    - module PIM feature failed search an employee
    - module PIM feature sucess delete employee
2. 
3.
4.
5.